HAYDAR KÜLEKCİ



Phone: +90 543 589 54 55 haydarkulekci@gmail.com

General Information

Birth Date : April 10, 1988 Gender/Marriage Status : Man/Married

Driver License : B

Address : Atatürk Bulv.. Cumhuriyet Mah. Bizimkent

Sitesi A-04 D:51 İstanbul/Beylikdüzü

Abstract

I am an application developer for web and mobile platforms. I worked on PHP, Python, NodeJS, Swift languages and mainly focused on PHP Frameworks (Slim Framework, Symphony 2), PHP Design Patterns (MVC, Singleton, Adapter, Registry, Dependency Integration, Decorator, ...etc). I also worked on SMPP v3.4 and SMPP v5.0 protocol, GSM 03.38, GSM 03.40 specifically.

IOS Core Bluetooth, Bluetooth LE and iBeacon are my hobbies.

Github:

@hkulekci

Linkedin:

<u>hkulekci</u>

StackOverflow:

kulekci

Twitter:

@kulekci

Web:

kulekci.net

Web:

scanf.info

Technologies

Likes:

PHP, PHP Framework, Python, Objective-C, Swift, Xcode, Javascript, NodeJS, MVC, Design Patterns, Bluetooth LE, IOS Core Bluetooth, iBeacon,

SMPP, Redis, MySQL

Dislikes:

Flash

Experiences

Web Developer - Ankara Univ. Graduate School of Health

Between : 2006-2009

Keywords: PHP, Javascript, Ajax

I am worked on http://sagbilens.ankara.edu.tr/ website and create a web based forms to transfer papers and documents of the department.

Web Developer - GardenTR Internet Hizmetleri

Between : 2007-2010

Keywords: PHP, MVC, CMS, Admin Panel, Slim Framework,

Co-Founder and PHP developer. I had worked on admin panel of content management system for GardenTR.

Team Leader and Application Developer - Viveka

Between: July 2011 - November 2013

Keywords: PHP, MVC, Opencart, E-Commerce, Git, Github, Wordpress,

Plesk, Linux, Team Management, Basecamp, Jira, Start-up

I worked as Linux Server Manager (Plesk), Git Server Manager, Release Manager and PHP Application Developer. I also worked on identifying problems and resolving conflicts with the team.

Co-Founder and Application Developer - Motivolog

Between : August 2013 - Current

Keywords: PHP, MVC, Design Patterns, Linux, Security, iOS, iOS Bluetooth

Core, Bluetooth-LE, iBeacon

I wrote all Motivolog web application as main developer. I worked on PHP and Slim framework with Motivolog. In motivolog web application, I an email notification system with service based PHP script.

Now I am working on iOS Application of the Motivolog. It is use iOS Core Bluetooth and Bluetooth LE.

Team Leader and Application Developer - Somedya

Between : April 2014 - November 2014

Keywords: Python, Tornado Web Server, PHP, PHP Framework, MVC,

MySQL, API, API Documentation

I worked as Team Leader in Somedya. I wrote documentation for projects and coordinate back-end and front-end teams to create a awesome platform with these documents. Mainly, we worked to create Somedya API and backend systems.

Education

Computer Engineering - Ankara University — 2006-2012

My Github Repos

Basic MVC for Slim Framework - https://github.com/hkulekci/basicmvc GitHub, Jul 2013 - Nov 2014; followed by 4 people

PHP FIG Standarts Translation - https://github.com/hkulekci/fig-standards GitHub, Jun 2013 - Jul 2014; followed by 3 people; forked 4 times

PHP light CLI Application Example - https://github.com/hkulekci/light-php-cli GitHub, Feb 2013 - Nov 2014; followed by 5 people

Opencart E-Commerce System Contribution - https://github.com/opencart/opencart/commits?author=hkulekci GitHub, Aug 2012 - Sep 2013

PHP The Right Way Translation - https://github.com/hkulekci/php-the-right-way

GitHub, Jul 2012 - Nov 2014; followed by 12 people; forked 16 times

Light Session Class (Wrapper) - https://github.com/hkulekci/session GitHub, Aug 2013

Learn X in Y minutes Translation - https://github.com/adambard/learnxinyminutes-docs/commits?author=hkulekci GitHub, Aug 2013 - Jun 2014